Rokaya amjaad

Baghdad , Iraq| 07815163645 rukayaamged733@gmail.com | LinkedIn | GitHub | @Ruqayaamjad (Telegram username)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Capo information technology company | (May 2022-Jun 2022)

I worked as (Front-End) web developer and as (Data Entry), in this period I designed and programmed many websites projects that helped me to Improve my design vision.

Freelance Web Developer (January 2022-April 2022)

- <u>Nitrogen Website</u>: nitrogen is an Iraqi science academy that aims to turn primary, intermediate, and secondary school science theoretical curricula into practical ones.
- <u>Glassedo Website</u>: specialized laser printing company, I was responsible for creating the design and the website for them.
- <u>Himma Website:</u> a community project that start with the Station last year, and I was in charge to design and create the website for them.

Space roaming company |(January 2020-January 2021)

- Worked as Front-End web developer, Build the company website interface (space roaming) and my design vision enabled the company to join Orange organization, one of the organizations specialized in developing start-up companies and business management.
- Manager of IOT projects.

PERSONAL SUMMARY

Web Developer and Senior Engineering student, Passionate in Technology and Programming field especially, had Two years of Experience in working as a Front-End web developer, I'm a fast learner and a very good team player that can Build very complex designs and implement them easily.

SKILLS & PROFICIENCIES

- HTML, CSS languages and dealing with Tailwind framework.
- JavaScript .
- React.js
- Vue.is
- Blender.
- WordPress.
- Figma.
- C++.
- Work with Arduino and IOT projects.
- Experienced in dealing with 3D printer machines.

Rokaya amjaad

Baghdad , Iraq| 07815163645 rukayaamged733@gmail.com | LinkedIn | GitHub | @Ruqayaamjad (Telegram username)

CERTIFICATE

- HAS certification in Front-End web development from (Re:Coded Organization) (certification link).
- HAS a certification in Internet Marketing Basics from Google (certification link).
- HAS a certification in Speak English Professionally In Person Online & On the Phone by Georgia Institute of Technology (certification link).
- HAS certification in Front-End web design from (IOT MAKER).
- HAS certification in IOT field from (IOT MAKER).
- HAS certification in 3D modeling and Design from (The Station) (certification link).

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

BAGHDAD UNIVERSITY /AUTOMATION MANUFACTURING ENGINEERING STUDENT /BORN in (2001-5-31).